Stanford University, Office of Student Activities, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional material, 1978-2004; Accession ARCH.2014-052
  - Volunteer student organization files, 1978-2004
    - Active
      - Educational Studies Program (ESP), 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Elijah Christian Cell Group at Stanford, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Electrolytes, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Emerge, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Engineers without Frontiers, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Enigma, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Epicureans at the GSB, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Episcopal Student Organization, 1993-2002 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Esface Enterprises, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Estonian Student Association, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Etruscan Anthropological Society, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - European Association at Stanford, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Everyday People, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - !Expression!, 1991-2002 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Familia, 1995-2002 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Family Medicine Interest Group, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Fellowship in Christ at Stanford (FICS), 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - The Feminist Collective, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - 49'ers Academy Teaching Team, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Forum for American-Chinese Exchange at Stanford, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Free the Angola 3 Coalition, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - French Stanford Students Association, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Future Alumni Consulting Team, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Global Entrepreneurs Challenge, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Go Club, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Golfer's Club, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Graduate Association for Minority Engineers, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Graduate Student Programming Board, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Greek Publications, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Green Party of Stanford, 1991-2003 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Green Team, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Grow, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - GSB Arts Media and Entertainment Club, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - GSB-Asia Forum, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - GSB-Christian Fellowship, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - GSB-Consulting Club, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - GSB Environmental Management Club, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - GSB Europe Club, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - GSB Governments and Politics Club, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 61)
      - GSB Healthcare and Biotech Club, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 62)
      - GSB Off Duty Club, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - GSB Orientation, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - GSB Outdoor Adventure Club, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - GSB PHD Association, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - GSB Private Equity Club, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - GSB Manufacturing Club, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Stanford Management Internship Fund, 1984-2003 (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - GSB Soccer Club, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - GSB Social Dance Club, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - GSB Student Association, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - GSB Student Show, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - GSB Trirunning Club, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 74)
      - GSB Ultimate Frisbee, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - GSB Venture Capital Club, 1994-2003 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - GSB Wine Circle, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - GSB Yearbook, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Habitat for Humanity, Stanford Chapter, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - HAPA Issues Forum, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 80)
      - Harvest Christian Fellowship, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 81)
      - Health Education for Life-Partnerships for Kids HELP, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 82)
      - Health Edu. For Women in Drug Treatment, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 83)
      - Hellenic Association at Stanford, 1986-2002 (Box 2, Folder 84)
      - Henry's Place, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 85)
      - Hindus Students Council, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 86)
      - Hip Hop Congress, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Hong Kong Student Association, 1987-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Indonesian Club at Stanford, 1994-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Interact at Stanford, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Stanford International Development Education Association (SIDEC), 1983-2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - International Medicine Interest Group, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - International Students Christian Outreach, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - International Undergraduate Community, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 1982-2003 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Intervarsity Grad, 1996-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Islamic Society of Stanford university (ISSU), 1978-2003 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Israel Folk Dancing, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Israeli Student Organization, 1993-2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - ITASA West Coast Conference, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Jam Pac'D, 1991-3003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Japan Karate Association at Stanford, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Jewish Business Students Association, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Jewish Graduate Students Association, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Jewish Leadership Council, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Kadima, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - The Kennedy Kosher Coop, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Kids with Dreams, 1998-2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Knitting Renaissance, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Korean-American Student Association, 1983-2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Korean Students Association, 1991-2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Kuumba Dance Ensemble, 1982-2003 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - KZSU, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Labor and Immigration Project, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Latin American Film Society of Stanford, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Latin American Student Assn, 1993-2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Latter-Day Saint Student Association, 1998-2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Law School Drama Society, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Lebanese Student Society, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Leland Stanford university Marching Band, 1982-2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - LGBT MEDS, 1998-2003 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Lit Magazine, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Los Hermanos de Stanford, 1994-2003 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Lutheran student Movement, 1991-2002 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - March of Dimes Collegiate Council, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Mariachi Cadenal de Stanford, 1994-2003 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Marketing Club-GSB, 1994-2003 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Masque, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Mechanical Engineering Graduate Women's Group, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Mensola, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Mixed Company, 1986-2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - MS and E Association -EESOR, 1983-2003 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - Muslim Students Awareness Network (MSAN), 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - Native American Big Sib/ Little Sib, 1991-2001 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Naged Ra'av, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - National Lawyers Guild, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Nepal Premedical Pediatric Clinical Internship, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Nepali Association at Stanford, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Network at Stanford, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Nigeria-Stanford Educational Resources Organization, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - Night Outreach, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Nomadic Shoe Store, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - OASIS-Organization of Arab American Students in Stanford, 1992-2002 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - OB/Gym Interest Group, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Organ Donor Education, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Orienteering Club, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Out 4 Biz, 1994-2003 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Outlaw, 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Outreach to Asian Immigrant Students, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Pacific Free Clinic, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - PALS, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Pakistanis at Stanford, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Parakalo Christian Ministry, 1988-2003 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Partnerships for Education, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Performance Automotive Engineering Club, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Performance for Peace, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Persian Student Association, 1993-2002 (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - Peruanos En Stanford, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - Photography and Digital Imaging Club, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - Public School Medical Scholars, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Project A.I.Y.M.E., 1993-2003 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - Project Dosti-Stanford, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - Project Excell, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Project Smiles, 1991-2002 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - Queer-Straight Social and political Alliance, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - Querillas, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Ram's Head, 1978-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Redefining Our Premed Experience at Stanford (ROPES), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Redwood Action Team at Stanford, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Redwood Outdoor Club, 1992-2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - ReJOYCE in Jesus Campus Fellowship, 1985-2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Resistance Art and Social Protest, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Roller Hockey at Stanford, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Romanian Student Association, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Russian Club at Stanford, 1997-2004 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Saheli, 1997-2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - SAIO Pow-Wow, 1987-2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Salsa!, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - SAT Success, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Scandinavians at Stanford, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Sexual Health Peer Resource Center, 1989-2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Shaking the Foundation Conference, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Singaporeans at Stanford, 1992-2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Sisters in Stanford, 1978-2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Six Degrees, the Stanford human rights magazine, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Slavic "What? Where? When?" Club, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Social Venture Club, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Society for International Affairs at Stanford, 1980-2002 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Students for Sustainable Building at Stanford, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Students for the Truth, 1992-2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Society of Black Scientists and Engineers, 1994-2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Society of Petroleum Engineers, 1988-2003 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Society of Women Engineers, 1979-2003 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Soul Sistah Magazine, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - South Africa Club, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - South Asian Preventative Health Outreach Program (SAPHOP), 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - South Asian Students Association (SASA), 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Sports Challenge International, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Sports Industry Network (SPIN), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Sports Managment Club, 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Spring Faire, 1990-2003 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Stage One, 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Step Out, 1996-2002 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - StanFair (Stanford Students for Fair Trade), 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - StreetLaw, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - StudentErgonomics.org, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Students United for Racial Equity, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Student Committee for Community Lawyering, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - Student Initiated Courses (SIC), 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Students for Environmental Action at Stanford (SEAS), 1982-2002 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Students of Color Coalition (SOCC), 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Student Organizing Committee for the Arts (SOCA), 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - SURE Escort, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - SUSE Student Guild, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Surf Association of Stanford, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Swingtime, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Table Tennis Club, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Table Talk, 1991-2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Taiwanese Cultural Society, 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Talisman, 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - TapDance at Stanford, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Technology Assist by Students, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Tau Beta Pi, 1996-2003 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Theatre Q, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - The Bridge, 1984-2003 (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - The Dualist, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - The Forum, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - The Giving Tree, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - The Mind's Eye, 1993-2002 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - The Retail Club, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - The Science Bus, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - The Stanford Daily, 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - The Stanford Progressive, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - The Stanford Music Society, 1996-2002 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - The Stanford Review, 1995-2002 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Together Each Achieves More (TEAM), 1989-2003 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - Undergraduate Philosophical Association, 1978-2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Ukranian Student Association at Stanford, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Undergraduate Chinese American Association, 1988-2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Unidas, 1996-2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Unitarian Universalists at Stanford, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - United States Student Association, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - United Students for Veterans' Health, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Urban Styles Dance Company, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - V-Day Stanford, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Venezuelan Association at Stanford, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Volunteers in Latin America (VILA), 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Wilderness Medicine, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Women's Health Interest Group, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Women in Computer Science, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Women Leaders of Tomorrow, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Women of Stanford Law, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Stanford Women's Rugby, 1978-2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Womenspeak, 1996-2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - World Peace Buddhists, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Women and Youth Supporting Each Other (WYSE), 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Yanyuan Club, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Yoga for Graduate Students, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Young at Heart, 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Young Communist League at Stanford, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Active, Stanford, 1978-2004
      - Stanford Aerobics and Yoga, 1992-2002 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Stanford Aikido Club, 1980-2003 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Stanford Alliance for Service Through the Arts (SASTA), 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Stanford Alpine Club, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Stanford Alpine Project, 1990-2002 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Stanford Alumni Mentoring, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Stanford Amateur Radio Club, 1979-2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Stanford American Indian Medical Students, 1989-2002 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Stanford American Indian Organization, 1978-2002 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Stanford Anthology for Youth, 1995-2002 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Stanford Arts Collective, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Stanford Asia Pacific Technology Group, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Stanford Asian American Activism Coalition, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Asian Baptist Student Koinonia, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Stanford Asian American Medical Students, 1989-2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Stanford Astrobiology Association, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Stanford Athletes and Kids United, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Stanford Astronomical Society, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Stanford Axe Committee, 1983-2003 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Stanford Badminton Team/Club, 1980-2003 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Stanford Balkan Student Association, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Stanford Ballroom Dance Club, 1978-2002 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Stanford Ballroom Dance Team, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Stanford Bhangra Team, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Stanford Bike Advocates, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Stanford Biodesign, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Stanford Black Premedical Organization, 1990-2003 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Stanford Bluegrass Club, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - Stanford Bowling Team, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Stanford British Society, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Stanford Business School Futurist Club, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Stanford Cambodian Cultural Association, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Stanford Canadian Club, 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Stanford Cardinal Broadcasting Network, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - SCBN-TV Studio Proposal, 1994 Feb 28 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Stanford Chamber Chorale, 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Hammer and Coffin - Chaparral, 1968-1978, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Stanford Chaparral, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Stanford Civil Liberties Union, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Stanford Chinese Institute of Engineers, 1983-2003 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Stanford Climbing Wall, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Stanford Club Sports, 1982-2002 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Stanford College Bowl Club, 1990-2003 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Stanford Community Carnival - Registrations, 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Stanford Community Farm, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Stanford Community for Peace and Justice, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Stanford Conservative Union, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Stanford Consulting, 1979-2003 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Stanford Contract Bridge Club, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Stanford Craft Guild, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      - Stanford Cricket Club, 1991-2002 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - Stanford Cycling Club, 1979-2003 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Stanford Debate, 1990-2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Stanford Democrats, 1979-2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Stanford Dressage Club, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Stanford Economics Association, 1993-2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Stanford Egyptian Association, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Stanford Engineering Association, 1989-2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Stanford Engineered Solutions, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Stanford Environmental Health Interest Group, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Stanford Environmental Law Society, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Stanford Environmental Representatives, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Stanford Equestrians, 1985-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Stanford ESL Partners, STEPS, 1991-2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Stanford Film Partners, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Stanford Figure Skating Club, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Stanford Fleet Street Singers, 1982-2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Stanford Gaming Society, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Stanford Garden Project, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Stanford German Students Association, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Stanford University Gospel Choir, 1980-2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Stanford GSB Golf Club, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Stanford GSB Asian Society, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Stanford GSB High Tech Club, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Stanford GSB Rugby Club, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - GSB Ski and Snowboard Club, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Stanford Hwimori, 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Stanford Improvisors (SIMPS), 1991-2003 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Stanford International Law Society, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Stanford In Government, 1991-2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Stanford India Association, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Stanford INFORMS, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - IEEE, 1981-2003 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Stanford-Israel Alliance, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Stanford Japanese Association, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Stanford Jazz Orchestra, 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Stanford Jewish Women's Collective, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Stanford Journal of International Relations, 1997-2003 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Stanford Judo Club, 1980-2002 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Stanford Jujitsu Club, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Stanford Kenpo Karate Association, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Stanford Kayak Club, 1981-2003 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Stanford Latino Business Association, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Stanford Latino Law Student Association (SLLSA), 1993-2002 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Stanford Law and Wine Society, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - Stanford Law and Technology Association, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - Stanford Law Review, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - Stanford Law School Democrats, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - Stanford Law Students Association, 1988-2002 (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - Stanford Martial Arts Program, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - Stanford Medical Minority Student Alliance, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 49)
      - Stanford Medical Student Association (SMSA), 1980-2002 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - Stanford Medical Students for Choice, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Stanford Men's Rugby, 1985-2002 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - Stanford Mendicants, 1979-2002 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Stanford Mock Trial, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Stanford Muay Thai, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Stanford NAACP, 1998-2004 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - SNAGS, 1988-2003 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Stanford Objectivist Club, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Stanford Opera Society, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Stanford Outdoor Outreach Program, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Stanford Outing Club, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Stanford Political Science Association, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Stanford Polo Club, 1981-2003 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - Stanford Pre-Law Society, 1991-2002 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - Stanford Premedical Association, 1988-2002 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Stanford Project on Nutrition (SPOON), 1987-2003 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Stanford Psi Chi, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Stanford Public Interest Law Foundation, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Stanford Quad, 1971-2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Stanford Racquetball Club, 1981-1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Stanford Ragapella, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Stanford Raza Medical Association, 1984-2003 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Stanford Republicans, 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Stanford Running Club, 1987-2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Stanford Serbian Student Society, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Stanford Queer Engineers and Scientists, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Stanford Savoyards, 1981-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Stanford Shakespeare Society, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Stanford Shuai-Chiao Kung Fu Club, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Stanford Shotokan, 1978-2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)